# Yu Guan Ting Thomas

# front-end developer

I am a driven and highly motivated software developer with a strong background in team leadership and effective communication. My past experience demonstrates rapid learning abilities and adaptability across various programming languages, making me a valuable asset in dynamic IT coding environments.

thisisthomasyu@gmail.com

thomasfishy.netlify.app/

github.com/ThisisFishy

Johor Bahru, Malaysia

in linkedin.com/in/guan-ting-yu-88b13b267

#### **EDUCATION**

# **HD Electronic and Information Engineering**The Hong Kong Polytechnic University

09/2018 - 03/2022 HongKong GPA: 2.98
Courses

 Object-Oriented Design And Programming - Database System

- Computer Programming

Intergrated Project

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Technician**

Tak Wa Medical Center

05/2022 - 12/2022

Масаи

#### **ORGANIZATIONS**

Student Organization Sports Affairs Committee (09/2019 - 09/2021)

President

Orientation Camp Organizing Committee (09/2019 - 09/2020)

President

### **SKILLS**



# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Personal Website (03/2023 - Present)

# **CERTIFICATES**

# HD Electronic and Information Engineering (09/2018 - 03/2022)

https://www.acvp.hk/verification/sharelinks/abdf99d0-9364-4fa3-a4d1-0c83682aafea

# JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (01/2023 - 03/2023)

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc950351b1-68bf-4a34-9363-d9d5ba7daad0/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures

#### Responsive Web Design (01/2023 - 03/2023)

https://freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc950351b1-68bf-4a34-9363-d9d5ba7daad0/responsive-web-design

### **LANGUAGES**

English Professional Working Proficiency Mandarin

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Cantonese

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

WEB3 BlockChain NFT Bartending